Episode 17
第 17 集
Brother Juqing.
巨庆兄。
I embroidered this myself.
这是我自己绣的。
are you okay.
你还好吗。
Your Highness is no longer interested in me.
殿下对我已经不感兴趣了。
Sooner or later she will allow me to leave.
迟早她会允许我离开。
My father arranged a marriage for me.
我父亲为我安排了一桩婚姻。
Please continue.
请继续。
And I wish you wealth
我祝你财富
And happiness.
和幸福。
you...
你...
Are you getting married?
你要结婚了吗？
Yes, next month.
是的，下个月。
When you asked me to take you with me
当你要求我带你一起去的时候
You said you didn't want to leave your family.
你说过你不想离开你的家人。
And I was afraid.
我很害怕。
And now you have come to rub salt in my wounds.
现在你却来在我的伤口上撒盐。
Nickname...
昵称...
Why did I fall in love with someone like you?
为什么我会爱上你这样的人？
Forget it.
忘了它。
I misjudged you.
我误判你了。
I wasn't lucky to have met you.
我并不幸运能够遇见你。
You are in charge of delivery.
你负责送货。
This time with Hwangcheong.
这次是和黄清。
Is it true?
这是真的吗？
yes
是的
But the purpose you are going for is
但你的目的是
Ruxin is making you completely forget about him.
如心正在让你彻底忘记他。
She is no longer young.
她已经不再年轻了。
One of her maids sent me a message.
她的一位女仆给我发了一条消息。
Saying that he still has feelings for you
说他对你还有感情
After all these years.
经过这么多年。
this time
这次
you will go
你将去
And make her forget about you completely.
并让她彻底忘记你。
What if I don't want to do it?
如果我不想这样做怎么办？
Then you will never see her again.
那么你就再也见不到她了。
Do not forget it
别忘记了
you and your family
你和你的家人
You are my slave.
你是我的奴隶。
Think of her.
想想她。
Between the servant's sons
仆人的儿子之间
And the lord of the Zong family
还有宗家家主
In Hwangcheong
位于黄清
Who is the better choice?
谁是更好的选择？
It's clear.
天气晴朗。
do as i say
照我说的做
Then I will return your contract to you
那我就把合同还给你
So you and your family will be free.
这样你和你的家人就会获得自由。
But if you insist on not doing that
但如果你坚持不这样做
Ruxin is never seen again.
再也没有见到如心。
You can take this chance
你可以借此机会
To say goodbye to her.
跟她说再见。
shake it
摇动它
I sincerely hope
我真诚地希望
you will buy
你会买
A life of wealth and glory.
财富和荣耀的一生。
to let go...
放手...
Lady, calm down.
女士，冷静点。
I agreed to come to the Bell Garden
我同意来贝尔花园
Because I didn't want my father to punish him.
因为我不想让父亲惩罚他。
???Ass... ???But what did I get?
???屁股... ???但是我得到了什么？
???Miss... ???What did I get?
???小姐... ???我得到了什么？
to let go.
放手。
Sir, Qin Lin is your servant.
先生，秦林是您的仆人。
There is a better choice.
有更好的选择。
I'm sure your father did the right thing.
我确信你父亲做的是对的。
A better choice?
更好的选择？
What other options do I have?
我还有什么其他选择？
I suffered for so long
我受了这么久的苦
And I got this result.
我得到了这个结果。
???Tell me please. ???me...
？？？请告诉我。？？？我...
Why am I the only one who feels miserable?
为什么只有我一个人觉得难过？
Calm down, girl...
冷静点，姑娘……
love is the most worthless thing
爱情是最不值钱的东西
oh my god.
我的天啊。
'Cause nothing goes right for me
因为没有什么事情适合我
I will make others feel what I feel.
我会让别人感受到我的感受。
Please take a seat, Second Aunt.
请二婶坐。
Did your second aunt come alone?
你二姨是一个人来的吗？
yes.
是的。
We haven't seen each other for a long time
我们已经很久没见面了
And I heard you missed us
我听说你想念我们
So I came right here.
所以我就来到了这里。
The bell garden is wonderful.
钟花园很棒。
The quality of everything here is much better
这里一切的质量都好多了
Than your uncle uses
比你叔叔用的
I thank Her Highness for her care.
感谢殿下的照顾。
Your mother praised your brother
你妈妈夸奖你弟弟
Because she was wise when she was in the city.
因为她在城里的时候就很聪明。
I think you are much wiser.
我认为你聪明得多。
Than her.
比她。
She lives with my sister.
她和我姐姐住在一起。
What she thinks is right.
她认为的就是对的。
My younger sister is more likable.
我的妹妹更讨人喜欢。
you're welcome.
不客气。
How does your sister compare to you?
你姐姐跟你相比怎么样？
You have spent a lot of time with His Highness.
您和殿下一起度过了很多时间。
very likely
很可能
You will be a member of the Jong family...
你将成为Jong家族的一员......
Anyway, my family
无论如何，我的家人
It will be up to you.
这将取决于你。
How are my cousins ​​and uncles?
我的表兄弟和叔叔们怎么样了？
I haven't seen them for a while
我有一段时间没见到他们了
And I miss them a little bit.
我有点想念他们。
are you okay. let me tell them
你还好吗。让我告诉他们
I'm coming to see you.
我来看你了。
That's a really good idea.
这真是个好主意。
I have something to ask my uncle.
我有件事要问叔叔。
As expected, my father contacts me often.
果然，父亲经常联系我。
Through him and letters.
通过他和信件。
It's true.
这是真的。
Have some tea, second aunt.
二姨，喝茶吧。
OK.
好的。
How have you been?
你最近怎么样？
can you tell?
你能告诉？
What scent is it today?
今天是什么气味？
It looks a little familiar to me
我看起来有点眼熟
But I can’t put my finger on it.
但我无法指指点点。
Mother, be careful.
妈妈，小心点。
It's a Chuseok scent.
这是中秋节的香味。
???Butler Whoa. ???You really are a deacon.
???管家哇。???你真是个执事。
I could tell even from afar.
即使从远处我也能看出来。
Come, baby.
宝宝来。
Mom, I will sit over there.
妈妈，我坐那边吧。
???long time no see. ???of course.
？？？好久不见。？？？当然。
How is your business?
你的生意怎么样？
???What happen? ???Please give it here.
？？？发生什么事？???请给这里。
Let’s eat and be healthy, okay?
让我们吃得健康，好吗？
Is he going to eat more?
他要吃更多吗？
I can't even pass through this wide passage.
这么宽阔的通道我都过不了。
Doesn't he know how fat he is?
他不知道自己有多胖吗？
Quiet. Isn't he your son?
安静的。他不是你儿子吗？
OK.
好的。
Chuseok incense is very expensive.
中秋香非常昂贵。
Ordinary deacons like us can't afford that at all.
像我们这样的普通执事根本负担不起。
I can only smell it from here.
我只能从这里闻到。
No wonder I didn't realize it.
难怪我没有意识到这一点。
yes. Hua Residence has a lot to offer.
是的。华公馆有很多值得一看的地方。
So he was able to identify it.
所以他能够识别出来。
That's why people say this.
这就是为什么人们这么说。
The Hua family is the second
华家是第二
Brings wealth to the Zhong family.
为钟氏家族带来财富。
There are also paintings and calligraphy.
还有书画。
Could you rate it?
您能给评价一下吗？
I'm sure...
我敢肯定...
Hello everyone.
大家好。
long time no see.
好久不见。
father. mother.
父亲。母亲。
Kian...
基安...
come...
来...
Kian.
基安.
Princess Royal has arrived.
长公主已经抵达。
Hello, Lord, Your Majesty.
您好，主啊，陛下。
Everyone please take your seats.
请大家就座。
Thank you, God.
感谢上帝。
I hope everyone has a happy Mid-Autumn Festival.
希望大家中秋节快乐。
Thank you for your hard work last year.
感谢您去年的辛勤工作。
Let me propose a toast.
让我提议干杯。
Make yourself at home.
请随便一点，就像在自己家一样。
Thank you, Your Majesty.
谢谢您，陛下。
???Please, teacher. ???I will help you.
???请老师。？？？我会帮你。
Qian, why are you sitting here?
钱，你怎么坐在这里？
eat your food
吃你的饭
I just want to talk to you.
我只是想和你谈谈。
I haven't seen you for a month.
我已经一个月没见到你了。
I think I lost weight again.
我想我又瘦了。
Let's talk after the banquet is over.
等宴会结束再说吧。
last time you were in my room
上次你在我房间时
You said you would come see me
你说过你会来看我
But you didn't.
但你没有。
Thank you for your courage in raising this issue.
感谢您有勇气提出这个问题。
Think about what you have done.
想想你做了什么。
And cause me less trouble
并减少我的麻烦
You don't need to worry that much.
你不需要担心那么多。
III didn't spoil anything this time.
III 这次没有破坏任何东西。
what? Isn’t that how it should be?
什么？难道不应该是这样吗？
Do you want me to compliment you?
想让我夸你吗？
One more word and I'll be done.
再多说一句话我就完事了。
OK.
好的。
Qian, we are at a banquet.
钱，我们在宴会上。
Could you be kinder to that person?
你能对那个人友善一点吗？
A month has passed
一个月过去了
I'm still waiting for my father's reply.
我还在等待父亲的答复。
So now I want to ask you directly.
所以现在我想直接问你。
Have you decided, Father?
神父，你决定了吗？
It wasn't easy for us
这对我们来说并不容易
To get to where we are today.
为了到达今天的位置。
Please don't mention this again.
请不要再提这件事了。
OK. I understand.
好的。我明白。
Father, I did my best.
爸爸，我已经尽力了。
Qian, I worry too much.
谦，我担心太多了。
Why don't you go home?
你为什么不回家？
And how many days off?
还有休息几天？
It doesn't have to be that way.
事情并不一定是这样的。
Where are you going?
你要去哪里？
Kian!
基安！
Who was she mad at?
她生谁的气了？
Are you leaving, Mr. Hua?
华先生，您要走了吗？
Lord.
主。
A divorce letter is sent
离婚信已发送
Later to your residence.
稍后前往您的住处。
???Divorce letter? ???yes.
？？？离婚信？？？？是的。
It has my stamp on it.
上面有我的印记。
Only then can you see the effect.
只有这样你才能看到效果。
Without signing your name.
没有署名。
Thank you, God.
感谢上帝。
I will go back and wait.
我会回去等待。
Hua Chen...
华晨...
Lord, we are in the garden of servants.
主啊，我们是在仆人的花园里。
Many people pass through this place.
很多人都会经过这个地方。
No one knows about divorce yet.
还没有人知道离婚这件事。
I don't want rumors to spread.
我不希望谣言传播。
This will also ruin your reputation.
这也会毁掉你的名誉。
Who is he?
他是谁？
He is Hua Rongzhou.
他就是华荣舟。
A guard at the servant's residence.
仆人住所的守卫。
He is like a block of wood.
他就像一块木头。
He made you angry because he was worried.
他让你生气是因为他担心。
For my reputation.
为了我的名誉。
Is your last name angry?
你的姓氏生气了吗？
we share the same last name
我们同姓
But we are not related.
但我们没有血缘关系。
My father told me not to go too far.
我父亲告诉我不要走得太远。
Lord, I'd better go back.
主啊，我还是回去吧。
Does that person look familiar to you?
你觉得那个人很熟悉吗？
He is the mistress's personal guard.
他是女主人的贴身侍卫。
I've seen him several times before.
我以前见过他很多次。
I think I saw him from very far away.
我想我从很远的地方看到了他。
Call Lin Jiang to confirm his identity.
给林江打电话确认身份。
Yes, Lord.
是的，主啊。
I know you are old
我知道你老了
If you stand up quickly for justice
如果你赶紧站出来维护正义
But you need to consider who you are dealing with.
但你需要考虑你正在和谁打交道。
If you insult the Lord
如果你侮辱了主
I may not be able to save you either.
我或许也救不了你。
The hostess, Guard Hua, said that.
女主人华护卫说道。
To protect your reputation.
为了保护您的声誉。
Finally, the news of divorce
终于传来离婚的消息
Nothing is known.
什么都不知道。
If someone saw it
如果有人看见了
Tongues will wag.
舌头会摇摆。
i know.
我知道。
Here it is.
这里是。
OK. Let's drink together.
好的。我们一起喝吧。
Kill Jong Hee-woo to avenge our family!
杀掉钟熙宇，为我们一家报仇！
Protect us Lord!
保护我们主啊！
Siu!
嘘！
run!
跑步！
Let's go, girl! hurry!
我们走吧，女孩！匆忙！
Let's go, girl!
我们走吧，女孩！
Let's go, Your Majesty!
我们走吧，陛下！
???Chen...Shen...! ???let's go!
？？？陈……沉……！？？？我们走吧！
Kian, let's go!
基恩，我们走吧！
???Honey... ​​???Hurry! let's go!
???亲爱的...​​???快点！我们走吧！
???hurry! ???Shen!
？？？匆忙！???沉！
mother...
母亲...
self...
自己...
???Go ahead and try it. ???What are you looking at?
？？？继续尝试。？？？你在看什么？
???go! ???hurry!
？？？去！？？？匆忙！
???Halongzhou! ???go! fast!
???下龙洲！？？？去！快速地！
let's go!
我们走吧！
???Shen... ???Brother.
???沉...???兄弟。
wake up. fast!
醒来。快速地！
???father. ???Qian...
？？？父亲。？？？谦...
???Qian! ???father!
？？？谦！？？？父亲！
go.
去。
Go and protect Cuizhu.
快去保护翠竹吧。
Am I their target?
我是他们的目标吗？
be careful!
当心！
???My love... ???Shen!
???我的爱... ???沉！
hurry.
匆忙。
Kian!
基安！
sibling!
兄弟！
???Shen! ???Shen!
???沉！???沉！
sibling.
兄弟。
Kian...
基安...
Did it hurt this much?
有这么痛吗？
When hit by an arrow?
什么时候被箭射中？
Why did you take the hit for me?
为什么你要替我承受打击？
Qian, you also protect me from the Master.
谦，你也保护我免受师父的伤害。
Didn't you?
你没有吗？
I am... I am your older brother.
我是……我是你的哥哥。
How can I stay still and do nothing?
我怎样才能保持安静，什么都不做？
When I see you in danger?
当我看到你有危险的时候？
sibling...
兄弟...
Kian, don't be afraid...
基恩，别害怕……
I'm fine.
我很好。
I will protect you.
我会保护你。
I'm with you. Hurt...
我和你在一起。伤害...
I'll take you home
我带你回家
No, brother. It'll be okay.
不，兄弟。会没事的。
I'll take you...
我带你...
Kian...
基安...
Kian!
基安！
Lord.
主。
The reception hall was cleaned.
接待大厅打扫得干干净净。
Were the assassins caught?
凶手被抓了吗？
There were many women in the hall.
大厅里有很多女人。
The guards made it difficult to catch them.
守卫很难抓住他们。
Most of the assassins fled.
大多数刺客逃跑了。
And some we caught
还有一些我们抓到的
He committed suicide by taking poison.
他服毒自杀了。
They also took some girls with them
他们还带着一些女孩
I ran away like a hostage.
我像人质一样逃跑了。
Who are they?
他们是谁？
Butler Lee's eldest daughter
李管家的大女儿
Butler Wu's wife
吴管家的妻子
To the concubine...
给小妾...
And the hostess.
还有女主人。
Magistrate Wang ordered the closure.
王县令下令查封。
And the Master is looking for them.
师父正在寻找他们。
Go and help the master.
快去帮助主人吧。
No, you can't, Lord.
不，你不能，主啊。
We are your personal security guards.
我们是您的贴身保安。
We don't show up until we're needed.
直到需要的时候我们才会出现。
Otherwise we are like regular security guards.
否则我们就像普通的保安一样。
Saving comes first.
储蓄是第一位的。
???Lord! ???Yes, Lord.
？？？主！???是的，主啊。
Let's go there. Go ahead and try it!
让我们去那儿。继续尝试！
There's nothing here, sir.
这里什么也没有，先生。
???find. ???All right.
？？？寻找。？？？好的。
Get out of the way.
走开。
No suspicious individuals were found, Master.
没有发现可疑人员，主人。
???Continue searching. ???All right.
???继续寻找。？？？好的。
There's nothing here either, Master.
这里也什么都没有，主人。
???There’s nothing here either. ??? Please keep searching.
???这里也什么都没有。??? 不停寻找。
All right.
好的。
Master, there is no suspicious person nearby.
主人，附近没有可疑的人。
Try a more thorough search.
尝试更彻底的搜索。
All right.
好的。
Teacher, are you okay?
老师，您还好吗？
If you want to save Hwacheon and Muyao
如果你想拯救华川和Muyao
Come alone to the cliffs of Eastern Town
独自来到东城悬崖
???Nanpung. ???I'm here.
???南丰。？？？我在这。
Continue your search with the men.
继续与男人一起寻找。
Where are you going, teacher? I will go with you.
老师你要去哪里？我和你一起去。
no. Continue your search.
不。继续您的搜索。
???Continue searching. ???All right.
???继续寻找。？？？好的。
Mu Yao.
穆瑶。
You finally woke up.
你终于醒了。
who are you?
你是谁？
What good would it do to tie me up?
把我绑起来有什么好处？
What if you want to kill me?
如果你想杀我怎么办？
It's not us who want to kill you.
不是我们想杀你。
What do you want?
你想要什么？
Do you have a grudge against me?
你跟我有仇吗？
You will find out later.
稍后你就会知道。
How is my brother?
我哥哥怎么样了？
Mu Yao, it finally happened.
慕瑶，终于出事了。
Go ahead and try it. Can you become like a normal person?
继续尝试。你能变得像正常人一样吗？
look down. It's a cliff!
向下看。这是悬崖！
???Jong-ye-ran.???Stop it!
???钟艺兰。???停下来！
Jong Ye-ran, how is my younger brother?
钟艺兰，我弟弟怎么样了？
What is Jong Ye like?
钟业是个什么样的人？
You came really quickly.
你来得真快。
But you'd better step back.
但你最好退后一步。
dare!
敢！
Do you know who you kidnapped?
你知道你绑架了谁吗？
We did it. Of course we know.
我们做到了。我们当然知道。
I came alone.
我一个人来的。
Tell me please. What do you want?
请告诉我。你想要什么？
Jongye-ran, please choose one.
宗艺兰，请选一个。
What nonsense are you talking about?
你在说什么废话？
What exactly do you want?
你到底想要什么？
We don't want anything.
我们什么都不想要。
We just want to see you and your family suffer.
我们只是想看到你和你的家人受苦。
Are you from the Ge family?
你是葛家的？
huh. you destroyed my family
呵呵。你毁了我的家庭
So you will definitely taste it today
所以今天你一定会尝到的
Losing someone you love!
失去一个你爱的人！
Stop!
停止！
You did it yourself.
你自己做的。
And if you want revenge
如果你想报仇
Wouldn't it be easier to just kill Zong Yeran?
直接杀了宗野然不是更容易吗？
Why did you kidnap us?
你为什么绑架我们？
I heard you love your wife
听说你爱你的妻子
And lots of concubines
还有很多妃嫔
Then it must be hard for you too.
那么你也一定很难。
Make a choice, right?
做出选择吧？
yes. Their lives are now in your hands.
是的。他们的生命现在掌握在你的手中。
choose one
选一个
And we're launching another one.
我们正在推出另一款产品。
But those who aren't chosen will become food
但那些没有被选中的人将会成为食物
For the fish in the lake.
为了湖里的鱼。
lake?
湖？
Which one would you choose?
你会选哪一个？
Why don't you choose anything?
你为什么不选择任何东西？
Save yourself from self-blame
让自己免于自责
Just pick one.
就选一个吧。
Who choreographed this?
这是谁编排的？
Did you just do this as a joke?
你这样做只是为了开玩笑吗？
Is this your first time being kidnapped?
这是你第一次被绑架吗？
Don't you know that you need to conduct a thorough search?
难道你不知道你需要进行彻底的搜索吗？
Before taking someone hostage?
在劫持某人之前？
You owe me something, Mu Yao.
慕瑶，你欠我的。
???government! ???Qian!
？？？政府！？？？谦！
Kian!
基安！
I never expected that one day I would be happy
没想到有一天我会幸福
I have been exiled.
我被流放了。
Thanks to Yubae, I learned to swim.
多亏了汤裴，我学会了游泳。
I can't stay here forever.
我不能永远留在这里。
The beasts will come out at night.
野兽会在晚上出来。
When in Lingnan
在岭南时
I've heard it once
我听过一次
That there are ordinary people
也有普通人
Living in the upper class
生活在上流社会
What are you trying to prove?
你想证明什么？
you should have stayed on the cliff
你应该留在悬崖上
And wait for Jong Ye-ran to make his choice.
等待金正恩做出选择。
Maybe he was too nervous.
也许他太紧张了。
That person made the wrong choice
那个人做了错误的选择
And I wouldn't be the one he gave up on.
我不会成为他放弃的那个人。
The terrain here is very rough.
这里的地形非常崎岖。
Even if Jong Ye-ran sends a man to look for me
即使钟艺兰派人来找我
It won't arrive that fast.
它不会那么快到达。
I suspect it's them.
我怀疑是他们。
I finally found you.
我终于找到你了。
I'm so glad it's you!
我很高兴是你！
I am really surprised now.
我现在真的很惊讶。
I didn't expect you to find me.
我没想到你会找到我。
I finally have someone by my side.
我的身边终于有人了。
I gave you this bracelet
我给了你这个手镯
for your self defense
为了你的自卫
I'm not saying you should commit suicide.
我并不是说你应该自杀。
Are you Hua Rongzhou?
你就是华荣舟？
No bone fractures.
没有骨折。
I think I need some ointment.
我想我需要一些药膏。
I will carry you on my back.
我会把你背在背上。
I can walk.
我可以走。
We have walked a long distance.
我们已经走了很长一段路。
Why can't I see anyone around?
为什么我看不到周围的人？
By the way, my brother...
顺便说一句，我的兄弟...
Get on my back.
到我背上来吧。
I'm fine.
我很好。
hurry.
匆忙。
I'm not good at drinking.
我不擅长喝酒。
I'm afraid that something embarrassing will happen later.
生怕以后会发生什么尴尬的事情。
Please take me downstairs.
请带我下楼。
Hostess, I know you can't hold your drink.
老板娘，我知道你喝不下去了。
???Go quickly. ???Then why did you do that...
？？？快去。？？？那你为什么要这么做……
what's the matter?
怎么了？
How did you know I was there?
你怎么知道我在那里？
What happened later?
后来发生了什么？
How is my brother?
我哥哥怎么样了？
After you and Mu-cheop were taken away
你和Mu-cheop被带走之后
I followed Master to the top of the mountain.
我跟随师父来到了山顶。
I don't really know what happened.
我真的不知道发生了什么事。
After the banquet is over
宴会结束后
And Mr. Hwa’s condition.
还有华先生的情况。
My sister will be okay, right?
我妹妹不会有事吧？
I said I would follow my teacher.
我说我会跟随我的老师。
to the top of the mountain
到山顶
But I didn't see you.
但我没有看到你。
You don't pay any attention to me.
你根本不理会我。
I'm used to it.
我习惯了。
No, that's not true.
不，那不是真的。
I was dizzy from falling over a cliff.
我从悬崖上掉下来，头晕目眩。
So I didn't notice you.
所以我没有注意到你。
Then do you remember...
那你还记得吗...
When did you first meet me?
你第一次见到我是什么时候？
Was it during ancestral rites?
是在祭祖的时候吗？
Just as I expected.
正如我所料。
What does it mean?
这是什么意思？
Mistress, do you remember?
小姐，你还记得吗？
Did you ask my name four times?
你问了我的名字四次了吗？
No, I...
不，我...
Why do I smell blood?
为什么我闻到了血腥味？
Are you hurt?
你受伤了吗？
It's just a small scratch.
这只是一个小划痕。
scratch? Did you get hurt in the woods?
划痕？你在树林里受伤了吗？
Drop me off. I can walk alone.
让我下车。我可以一个人走。
I have medicine.
我有药。
But how did you get here?
但你是怎么到这里的？
But why were you alone?
但为什么只有你一个人？
Who else did you expect to see?
您还希望见到谁？
Watch your tone!
注意你的语气！
How dare you say that to me?
你怎么敢对我这么说？
How rude! I am your mistress.
太粗鲁了！我是你的情妇。
You're divorced now, right?
你现在已经离婚了，对吗？
me...
我...
I'm older than you
我比你大
So you still have to respect me.
所以你还是要尊重我。
What should I call you...
我应该怎么称呼你...
After divorce?
离婚后？
That's right.
没错。
When they leave Hwangcheong with me
当他们和我一起离开黄清
Should they call me Miss?
他们应该叫我小姐吗？
But I wish they were free
但我希望它们是免费的
Live your own life.
过自己的生活。
Or has it never crossed your mind?
或者你从来没有想到过？
to take me with you
带我一起去
When leaving the species residence?
什么时候离开物种住所？
That's not true.
这不是真的。
For Tsuiju
前往翠州
I'll take you from your servant's residence.
我会带你离开你仆人的住所。
Why did it stop? Are you tired?
为什么停了？你累了吗？
I said I could walk by myself.
我说我可以自己走。
Get some rest. Hurt...
休息一下。伤害...
Don't match me with Cuizhu again.
别再把我和翠竹撮合了。
You can play in the yard
可以在院子里玩
Or when you're attacked
或者当你受到攻击时
I didn't want you to push me out to Cuizhu.
我不想让你把我推到翠竹去。
I told you to rescue Cui Ju. You heard me.
我叫你去救崔菊。你听到了。
Then why didn't you do it...
那你为什么不这么做呢...
Because I like someone.
因为我喜欢一个人。
Who is she?
她是谁？
Is that person in my house?
那个人在我家吗？
yes.
是的。
It's not kuijou. Are you Qianzhi?
这不是奎乔。你是千智吗？
???No ???Yinxing?
???没有???银杏？
no.
不。
I named everyone in my house.
我给家里每个人都起了名字。
Don't say it's me.
别说是我
Say it.
说吧。
Did you say something?
你说了什么吗？
Did you just say something?
你刚才有说什么吗？
you are a handsome man
你是一个英俊的男人
But to be clear:
但要明确的是：
I am no longer interested in worldly pleasures
我不再对世俗的享乐感兴趣
And I don't feel like falling in love
我不想坠入爱河
needless to mention
不用说
I don't like men younger than me.
我不喜欢比我年轻的男人。
If there is someone like Huarongzhou
如果有一个像华容舟那样的人
In a past life
在前世
The person who protected me like his life depended on it.
那个像生命一样保护我的人就靠它了。
Had I made all those mistakes?
我犯了所有这些错误吗？
Mistress, can I stop being your bodyguard?
小姐，我可以不再做你的保镖了吗？
After I help you get what you want?
我帮你得到你想要的东西之后？
Of course you can. You are a free man.
当然可以。你是一个自由的人。
But how do I know what I want?
但我怎么知道我想要什么？
Why are you silent again?
你怎么又沉默了？
Say it.
说吧。
Isn't this my room in Qianzhi Hua Residence?
这不是我千之花公馆的房间吗？
Yes that's right.
恩，那就对了。
Hua Rongzhou brought me here?
华荣舟带我来的？
yes.
是的。
oh my god. I was confused for a while.
我的天啊。我一时糊涂了。
I thought I was reborn.
我以为我重生了。
By the way, how is my brother?
顺便问一下，我弟弟怎么样了？
I believe he wasn't seriously hurt.
我相信他没有受重伤。
Qianzhi.
Qianzhi.
Why are you crying?
你哭什么？
Hostess, Master Hwayoung...
女主人，华英大师……
government!
政府！
Stop.
停止。
Where is my brother?
我的兄弟在哪里？
that...
那...
Bonus video
奖励视频
tell the chef to get ready
告诉厨师准备好
Bamboo shoot soup for Qi Ruxin.
竹笋汤为气入心。
It's her favorite dish.
这是她最喜欢的菜。
Come to think of it, that person didn't eat anything.
想想看，那个人什么也没吃。
Yes, Your Majesty.
是的，陛下。
Throw it away.
把它扔掉。
yes.
是的。
What happened to that girl?
那个女孩怎么了？